Here are 6 sections of a CISTR where a mixer is creating a suspension of copper particles in water. 
Section number corresponds to how far away the section is from the center of coordinates.
x1 is the supplementary cone bottom angle of the reactor
x2, x3 and x4 are spatial coordinates inside the reactor
y1 is concentration of copper particles, Npart/m3
y2 is velocity of particles, m/s
y3 is vorticity, 1/s
y4 is kinetic energy of turbulent pulsations, m^2/s^2
y5 is rate of dissipation of turbulent energy, m^2/s^3
y6 is eddy viscosity, Pa*s

Здесь представлены 6 сечений реактора идеального смешения, в котором мешалка создает суспензию частиц меди в воде.
Порядковый номер сечения указывает на расстояние сечения от центра координат, располагающегося в центре реактора.
х1 - смежный угол конуса днища реактора
х2, х3, х4 - пространственные координаты внутри реактора
у1 - концентрация частиц меди, Nчаст/м3
у2 - скорость частиц, м/с
у3 - завихренность, 1/с
у4 - кинетическая энергия турбулентных пульсаций, м^2/с^2
у5 - скорость диссипации турбулентной энергии, м^2/с^3
у6 - динамический коэффициент турбулентной вязкости, Па*с